<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-04-18T13:41:33-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Traveling Historian</title><subtitle>Artificial Intelligence trends and concepts made easy.</subtitle><author><name>William Mattingly</name></author><entry><title type="html">Kobe: Not just for Beef</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/kobe-travel-guide.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kobe: Not just for Beef" /><published>2024-03-24T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-03-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/kobe-travel-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/kobe-travel-guide.html"><![CDATA[<p>Kobe, the vibrant port city nestled on the north side of Osaka Bay, serves as a stunning gateway where Eastern traditions meet Western modernity. Just a short train ride from Osaka, Kobe offers a treasure trove of experiences, from indulging in world-famous Kobe beef to exploring ancient shrines and bustling night markets. Follow our journey through Kobe as we uncover the best of this enchanting city in just one day.</p>

<center><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9aI5joOuiPQ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></center>

<p>We started our adventure by taking a train from Osaka. The train journey is straightforward and scenic, setting the tone for a day of exploration. Upon arrival, we navigated Kobe’s main streets, which are lined with shops and eateries, all easily accessible from the central train station.</p>

<p>No visit to Kobe is complete without tasting its legendary beef. We dined at a local restaurant renowned for its premium Kobe beef, enjoying a multi-course meal that was both a culinary and a visual spectacle. The tender and flavorful beef, cooked right in front of us, was undoubtedly the highlight of our meal.</p>

<p>Next, we visited one of Japan’s oldest Shinto shrines, dating back to the 3rd century. The shrine, built by Empress Jingu, offers a peaceful retreat filled with historical significance. Just behind the shrine lies a serene urban forest, perfect for a quiet stroll away from the city bustle.</p>

<center><iframe src="https://www.google.com/maps/d/embed?mid=1r_Wot6CKPYbGg0UZ2lKyNPmkReqEGZQ" width="640" height="480"></iframe></center>

<p>In the afternoon, we refreshed ourselves at a quaint coffee shop known for its exceptional cinnamon cappuccino. The café’s ambiance transported us to a cozy corner of Western Europe, providing a delightful break with its aromatic brews and charming decor.</p>

<p>Our journey continued in Kitano, a district famous for its Western-style architecture. This area, once home to foreign settlers, features a variety of architectural styles and offers panoramic views of Kobe below. The blend of cultures here is a testament to Kobe’s cosmopolitan history.
We paid our respects at the moving 1995 Kobe Earthquake Memorial by the port. This poignant site commemorates one of the most devastating natural disasters in Japan’s history and provides a somber reminder of the resilience of the people of Kobe.</p>

<p>As evening fell, we explored Kobe’s Chinatown, where the energy is magnetic. The area is a hub of activity at night, with shops and restaurants that bring a slice of China to Japan. It’s an ideal place to soak in the lively atmosphere and enjoy some street food before heading back to Osaka.</p>

<p>Our day trip to Kobe was filled with diverse experiences, from gourmet dining and historical visits to enjoying the natural and architectural beauty of the city. Kobe is a city that proudly displays its heritage and its modern advancements, making it a must-visit for anyone traveling through Japan.</p>]]></content><author><name>William Mattingly</name></author><category term="trip planning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's explore Kobe and its many offerings, making it the ideal day trip from Osaka.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I’m going on an adventure!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/starting-the-adventure-copy-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I’m going on an adventure!" /><published>2024-01-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2024-01-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/starting-the-adventure%20copy%202</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/starting-the-adventure-copy-2.html"><![CDATA[<p>With our Christmas markets coming to an end, and the new year here, it’s time to announce the plans for the first half of 2024. This year, we’ll be traveling to Fiji, Australia, New Zealand, Japan, South Korea, Netherlands, Germany, France, and Italy. This is the first time I’ve had to pack for 4 seasons across both hemispheres. And this time, I’m only bringing my backpack…</p>

<p>Part of our goal this year was to explore new parts of the world we’d never seen. Another goal was to see all seven continents. By June, we will have been to four continents, with plans to visit South America in the July/August and Antartica in December.</p>

<p>As usual, I’ll be bringing you some travel tips and video content from historical sites. Stay tuned!</p>]]></content><author><name>William Mattingly</name></author><category term="trip planning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, I'll be traveling across Oceania, Australia, Asia, and Europe. What will I be packing? What are my travel plans? Here's an outline.]]></summary></entry></feed>